<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NYC Tour</string>
    <string name="tab_text_attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="tab_text_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tab_text_public">Public Places</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="image_desc_text">Thumbnail image</string>
    <string name="terminals">Terminals</string>
    <string name="central_park">Central Park</string>
    <string name="mahattan">Manhattan</string>
    <string name="brooklyn">Brooklyn</string>
    <string name="bryant_park">Bryant Park</string>
    <string name="dumbo">Dumbo</string>
    <string name="centra_park_desc">Central Park is a visual masterpiece created by landscape designer Frederick Law Olmsted and architect Calvert Vaux. It has gone through major developments and restoration over time to carry on its initial purpose as an open-air oasis for a metropolitan city. No matter the season or reason for your visit, this national historic landmark is a setting for enjoying many pursuits.</string>
    <string name="bryant_park_desc">Bryant Park is a beloved, year-round New York City destination. Known as Manhattan\'s Town Square, the park is famous for its lush seasonal gardens, free activities, world class restrooms, and al fresco dining. Located adjacent to the New York Public Library and surrounded by iconic skyscrapers, Bryant Park is visited by more than six million people each year and is one of the busiest public spaces in the world.</string>
    <string name="dumbo_desc">Trendy Dumbo\'s cobblestone streets and converted Brooklyn warehouse buildings are the backdrop for independent boutiques, high-end restaurants and trendy cafes. Near the waterfront, St. Ann\'s Warehouse, in a former tobacco factory, is the heart of a thriving performance and gallery scene.</string>
    <string name="katz_deli">Katz\'s Delicatessen</string>
    <string name="juliana_pizza">Juliana\'s Pizza</string>
    <string name="brooklyn_brewery">Brooklyn Brewery</string>
    <string name="katz_deli_desc">Katz’s is the undisputed pastrami king of NYC. This sprawling LES institution has been serving thick-cut, meltingly tender pastrami on rye since 1888 and doesn’t show any signs of slowing down.</string>
    <string name="juliana_pizza_desc">Juliana\'s heralds  the return of Patsy Grimaldi, New York City’s most celebrated pizza proprietor: not only to the NYC restaurant scene, but to 19 Old Fulton Street, the original location under the Brooklyn Bridge</string>
    <string name="brooklyn_brewery_desc">Brooklyn Brewery makes beer. Good beer. Not only does it taste good and make your meal better but we like to think that since its founding in 1988, Brooklyn Brewery has brewed flavorful beers that enrich the life, tradition and culture of the communities it serves.</string>
    <string name="coney_island">Coney Island - Stillwell Avenue</string>
    <string name="queens">Queens</string>
    <string name="grand_central">Grand Central - 42nd Street</string>
    <string name="south_ferry">South Ferry / Whitehall Street</string>
    <string name="flushing">Flushing - Main Street</string>
    <string name="broadway_junction">Broadway Junction</string>
    <string name="coney_island_desc">Acting as the railroad-south terminus for the D, F, N, and Q trains. The large facility, originally built in 1919, was designed at a time when Coney Island was the primary summer resort area for the New York metropolitan area, with all of the rail lines in southern Brooklyn funneling service to the area. It is one of the largest elevated transportation terminals in the world.</string>
    <string name="broadway_junction_desc">New York City Subway station complex shared by the elevated BMT Canarsie and BMT Jamaica Lines, and the underground IND Fulton Street Line. Throughout the history of the area, this has been a key junction point between various different rail lines. What is now Broadway Junction sits atop the historical Jamaica Pass, the junction of the modern Broadway, Fulton Street, and Jamaica Avenue. The Pass is where these roads passed through the valleys of the area, which are part of the terminal moraine created by the Wisconsin glaciation.</string>
    <string name="flushing_desc">The station is located in Downtown Flushing, also known as Flushing Chinatown, one of New York City\'s largest Asian enclaves.</string>
    <string name="south_ferry_desc">Subway station complex in the Manhattan neighborhood of Financial District, under Battery Park. The complex is shared by the IRT Broadway–Seventh Avenue Line and the BMT Broadway Line.</string>
    <string name="grand_central_desc">It is the second busiest station in the 424-station system, with 46,121,509 passengers in 2016.</string>
    <string name="statue_of_liberty">Statue of Liberty</string>
    <string name="moma">Museum of Modern Art</string>
    <string name="wtc">One World Trade Center</string>
    <string name="statue_of_liberty_desc">\"The Statue of Liberty Enlightening the World\" was a gift of friendship from the people of France to the United States and is recognized as a universal symbol of freedom and democracy. The Statue of Liberty was dedicated on October 28, 1886.  It was designated as a National Monument in 1924.  Employees of the National Park Service have been caring for the colossal copper statue since 1933.</string>
    <string name="moma_desc">MoMA is a place that fuels creativity, ignites minds, and provides inspiration. Its extraordinary exhibitions and collection of modern and contemporary art are dedicated to helping you understand and enjoy the art of our time.</string>
    <string name="wtc_desc">One World Trade Center is the main building of the rebuilt World Trade Center complex in Lower Manhattan, New York City. It is the tallest building in the Western Hemisphere, and the sixth-tallest in the world.</string>
</resources>
